<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<game>	
	<developer>cyborgDino</developer>
	<title>Asteroid Soccer 2014</title>
	<release-date>November 12, 2013</release-date>
	<website>http://www.asteroidsoccer.com</website>
	<based-in>Los Angeles, CA</based-in>
	
	<press-contact>contact@cyborgdino.com</press-contact>
	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>OUYA</name>
			<link>https://www.ouya.tv/game/Amazing-Frog-The-Hopping-Dead/</link>
		</platform>
	</platforms>

	<socials>
		<social>
			<name>twitter.com/cyborgdino</name>
			<link>twitter.com/cyborgdino</link>
		</social>
<!-- 		<social>
			<name>Skype</name>
			<link>callto:MySkypeName</link>
		</social>
 -->	
	</socials>

	<description>	
		In the future, scientists have scientifically invented Asteroid Soccer! Designed to be the absolutely perfect sport, it has rendered all other sports obsolete in the year 2014. The rules are simple. Pilot your Viper Fighter XJ42 and push the giant space ball into your opponent's goal by any means possible. Equip yourself with the most overpowered weapons, thrusters, bombs, and anything you can find on the space-field so that you can dodge, crash, blast, and explode your way to victory.
	</description>
		
	<histories>
		<history>
			<header>Birth</header>
			<text>Asteroid Soccer was conceived at the artists collective known as Glitch City.  It is also the home of other notable projects such as Skulls of the Shogun, Kachina, Quadrilateral Cowboy and Hyper Light Drifter. The idea for this game was born one day at Glitch City during one of our communal brainstorming sessions. General consensus amongst members was that sports games were not their bag. A few of the members took up the challenge to come up with a sports game that core gamers would want to play. Leading the project was Arjun Prakash and Seiji Tanaka formerly of That Game Company. Once the initial prototype was created, we realized we had a crazy fun co-op party game on our hands. A visit from Kelly Santiago left Glitch City with an OUYA.  We felt this console was the perfect home for Asteroid Soccer due to its strong lineup of local multiplayer games.</text>
		</history>
		<history>
			<header>Ouya Early Access</header>
			<text>For the release of the game we are trying something new that has never been done on the OUYA--an early access model in the vain of the steam store.  Although the core of the game is fully functional and fun, we would like to create more content with expanded modes. By offering the game at 25% discount for $2.99, we hope to subsidize the remainder of the development cycle.</text>
		</history>
	</histories>


	<earlyaccess>
		<price>
			<currency>USD</currency>
			<value>$2.99</value>
		</price>
	</earlyaccess>
	
	<prices>
		<price>
			<currency>USD</currency>
			<value>$3.99</value>
		</price>
<!-- 		<price>
			<currency>EUR</currency>
			<value>€1.59</value>
		</price>
		<price>
			<currency>CAD</currency>
			<value>$1.99</value>
		</price>				
		<price>
			<currency>GBP</currency>
			<value>£1.29</value>
		</price>
 -->	</prices>

	<features>
		<feature>Fast-paced retro arcade action with simple controls driven by 2-6 local multiplayer co-op.</feature>
		<feature>Genre bending game combining a shmup and soccer.</feature>
		<feature>Featuring multiple modes with different types of gameplay.</feature>
		<feature>Mind altering Waltz Match: one player controls two ships at a time!</feature>
		<feature>Coming soon: power-ups for varying degrees of havoc and chaos.</feature>
		<feature>Original project from the Glitch City collective.</feature>
	</features>
		
	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>Asteroid Soccer 2014 - Debut Trailer</name>
			<youtube>2feudvK7y2g</youtube>
		</trailer>
	</trailers>
	
	<awards>
		<award>
			<description>Winnter of the nobel sports peace prize</description>
			<info>Mars colony #837, 20 October, 2025</info>
		</award>
		<award>
			<description>Nomination for the best retro game of an asteroid nature</description>
			<info>Pyongyang, 4 December, 2017</info>
		</award>
		<award>
			<description>Winner of a highly relevant contest.</description>
			<info>Important Location, 20 October, 1988</info>
		</award>
	</awards>
	
	<quotes>
		<quote>
			<description>This is like the FIFA of the OUYA</description>
			<name>Borut Pfifer</name>
			<website>Skulls of the Shogun</website>
			<link>http://skullsoftheshogun.com/</link>
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<description>I dont see the website name in your trailer</description>
			<name>Brendon Chung</name>
			<website>Blendo Games</website>
			<link>http://blendogames.com/</link>
		</quote>
		<quote>
			<description>What is something I said about it?</description>
			<name>Ben Esposito</name>
			<website>Arcane Kids</website>
			<link>http://arcanekids.com/</link>
		</quote>
	</quotes>
	
 	<additionals>
		<additional>
			<title>Boilerplate</title>
			<description>cyborgDino is a member of the Glitch City artist collective.</description>
			<link>http://glitchcity.org/</link>
		</additional>
	</additionals>
 
	<credits>
		<credit>
			<person>Archie Prakash</person>
			<role>Lead Designer, Programmer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Seiji Tanaka</person>
			<role>Lead Programmer, Artist</role>
		</credit>
	</credits>
	
	<contacts>
		<contact>
			<name>Inquiries</name>
			<mail>contact@cyborgdino.com</mail>
		</contact>
		<contact>
			<name>Twitter</name>
			<link>http://twitter.com/cyborgdino</link>
		</contact>
<!-- 		<contact>
			<name>Facebook</name>
			<link>http://facebook.com/MyCompanyName</link>
		</contact>
 -->		<contact>
			<name>Web</name>
			<link>www.cyborgdino.com</link>
		</contact>
	</contacts>
</game>